[♪ opening theme song playing]
[HANA] "Dear Yuru, I have your
fake sister and a village child.
On the next full moon
at the Hour of the Boar,
come to Fujimurayama
Warehouse One."
[Yuru grunts]
[Yozakura growls]
[YURU] How? Where did this thing
come from?
Dera! Shoot this thing!
[all gasp]
[grunts]
[DERA] Yuru!
[Yuru grunts]
[IVAN] None of these people
had to die
if Yuru had come alone
like I told him.
And if you're not to blame,
whoever was the master
of those sword daemons
before you spilled their blood.
I can smell Mine and Nagisa
on those blades.
[Dera grunts]
[Ivan chuckles]
[RIGHT] Dera,
leave us and find Yuru.
We'll take this man
and his daemons alive.
[LEFT] A gift for our master.
[Yuru gasps]
[Yozakura growls]
[both grunt]
-[Shingo gasps]
-What the...
♪
[YURU] Smoke signals.
[grunts]
Danji's asking us to help him.
[Azami cries]
[ASA (FAKE)]
Azami, it'll be okay.
Someone's on their way
to save us right now.
Who is it?
My brother.
[both grunting]
-You really came!
-Yuru!
So I thought I'd find
my brother here.
[Asa (fake) and Azami trembling]
-It's Asa!
-Get her!
[growling]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[both screaming]
[Embrace growls]
[FUYUKI] Thank you.
[gasps] So easily?
Isn't Asa supposed to be
weaker in the nighttime?
Wait, I thought so, too!
So that means
Break is just that strong!
[both gasping]
-Yin and Yang...
-[both squeal]
...grab those two.
[both gasp]
[BOTH] Uh?
-[both gasping]
-[ASA] Hey.
[both yelp]
[ASA (FAKE)]
What's going on here?
Any other hostages?
Or is it just her? Answer me.
Azami's the only village child
they took.
But she's got
nothing to do with this!
She's just
an innocent bystander!
If you want revenge,
leave her out.
[Asa grunts]
I've got a lot of things to say.
So much to say, but later.
For now,
just stay where you are.
I'll let you out
when I'm done working.
And as soon as I do,
you will tell my brother
everything.
And I mean everything!
Leave nothing out!
Hey, Yin and Yang?
You can let go of me now.
I beg you,
don't lie to Yuru anymore.
[both gasp softly]
♪
[Embrace growling]
[both gasping]
[MAN 1] Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[MAN 2] There's no way.
[both whimpering]
[laughs]
[men screaming]
[MAN 1] Who is this woman?
She took my daemons!
[MAN 2] I'm just a normal dude!
Spare me!
[both screaming]
[ALL] Uh?
So this is Oedo Transport.
Seems like Mamegarasu's intel
was right on the money.
[YURU] That's gotta be where
they're keeping the hostages.
It is so loud in there.
Mm-hmm. The real Asa's inside
tearing it apart.
Hmm? Uh?
[YURU] Huh.
[whimpers]
[cries]
Yuru, you came to save me.
Huh? Don't be stupid.
Do you really think
I'd come all this way
to save some
whiny little punk like you?
Hey, get off of me.
Aw. I heard about
a couple people
wearing suits walking their dog.
Yeah, you've gotta be
those aliens
-Ken told me about.
-[Yuru continues indistinctly]
[FEMALE DAEMON] We're daemons.
[MALE DAEMON] Nice to meet you.
[DERA] Then over there,
that's gotta be Danji?
I've never seen
his true form before.
Right and Left
are busy somewhere,
pursuing a lead they found
on my mom and dad.
The only reason I'm here
is because I trust them
to take care of themselves.
-[Dera chuckles]
-This was a simple process
of elimination.
I didn't come to save you.
Why are you laughing, Dera?
Back off!
[ALL] Huh?
[MAN 1] Someone help! [screams]
But man...
If Asa's already got things
covered here, why'd I bother?
[men groaning]
Do you think everyone's okay
at the manor?
They've got enough manpower.
I'm sure they're fine.
Damn. No one said
Break was gonna be here, too.
You shouldn't believe
everything you hear so easily.
I know it was all
part of the plan,
but acting like a broken record?
Not easy.
What? So you were acting?
Could have fooled me.
I want to see my brother.
Of course that was acting.
Plus, Ai really hammed it up.
You think? It seemed to me
like she had your impression
down pat.
Someone had to inform me
when she took your place.
I didn't have a clue at all.
[Asa gasps]
I hear my brother's voice!
-[grunts]
-And now you're hearing things?
Oof, poor girl.
I knew I'd find you out here!
Uh? How the hell?
[ASA] Are you all right, Yuru?
You haven't died?
Who's got time to die?
I'm way too busy living!
[Asa chuckles]
[FUYUKI] He really was there.
Did you find the village kid
they were holding hostage?
Plus there's Asa.
Well, the fake one.
Yep, no worries.
I put them both
somewhere they would be safe.
Praise me! And gimme a hug!
Why don't you ask Right?
He's great at 'em.
[chuckles]
[FEMALE DAEMON] Your other half
and the kid are just fine.
[MALE DAEMON]
How about it, Danji?
-That's great news.
-[dog panting]
-Yuru.
-Uh?
[DANJI (TSUGAI)]
Thank you for coming.
The heck did I do?
You should save your thanks
for Asa.
Yeah. I'll thank her, too.
I was just so happy to see
you actually came. [sniffles]
[Yuru grunts softly]
[DANJI (TSUGAI)] Thanks, Yuru.
And sorry.
I won't lie to you anymore.
[cries]
[Yuru grunts softly]
[YURU] Hmm.
♪
[Danji (Tsugai) shouting]
And Asa... Thank you, too!
Huh? Whoa, hey, back off!
I didn't do it for you!
I'm only here 'cause
I wanted to save Yuru!
Plus, this mission supported
the Kagemoris!
In fact, I hope Higashi Village
gets wiped off the map!
You and your sister
are a lot alike.
What? How so?
The violent maniac part?
Hey, Big Daddy Kagemori!
You'll find Shingo
at the TT Logistics office!
We're a little busy here.
Mind taking care of him?
Oh, can do.
Let's go. We're not done.
[BOTH] Sir.
Hey, Yuru!
I'll see you soon, 'kay?
Later.
[exclaims]
[cries]
[ASA] Such a casual response
for his little sister! [cries]
And hey! He actually agreed
we'd meet up later!
-Very moving.
-I'm so happy I can't walk.
[DANJI (TSUGAI)]
By the way, Yuru,
you mentioned something
about Left and Right
having a lead on your parents.
What's that about?
Oh, yeah.
I guess you wouldn't know
they went missing
after they came down
the mountain.
But we might just have a clue.
Left and Right are in the middle
of fighting a guy
who knows something.
I'd better head there.
-Idiot.
-Wait, what?
Why wouldn't you go to them
before me?
Who do you think
you're calling an idiot?
You just said they're missing.
That should always be
your top priority.
You've gotta value
your ma and pa!
And who says I don't?
Look, emotions are high,
and I could really do
without being called an idiot.
You know your precious
Asa-In-A-Cell was a phony.
And I'd been playing you
for a fool all these years, too!
So of course I'd call you
an idiot for choosing us!
You are!
Ah! You guys
did string me along.
Thanks for reminding me
of that, you big jerk!
-You're an idiot.
-[YURU] Shut up, idiot!
[FEMALE DAEMON]
Seems like they made up.
-[MALE DAEMON] Seems so.
-[YURU] I'm not an idiot.
You're an idiot, idiot!
[GUARD] More to do?
Aw, man.
I just think I need a vacation.
This job is exhausting.
[brakes squeak]
[GUARD] Come on.
It's out of batteries?
HQ told me
they restocked everything.
[groans]
And someone really bothered
busting one of these
old warehouses open. Great.
The thieves must have used
some heavy-duty stuff.
Hmm?
[sighs]
How annoying.
[lever clunks]
♪
[guard trembling]
[thuds]
[panting]
Who do we call? An ambulance?
No way. The police! HQ! HQ!
Something terrible's
happened here!
[running footsteps]
This is a rifle, Yuru.
It's the long-range weapon
you saw me use
in our fight
against Tenaga-Ashinaga.
A single shot from this baby
could very well be lethal.
If I plug an ordinary person
with it,
the shock alone might kill them
even if I miss their vitals.
Just keep in mind
that if I do have to use this,
I can't guarantee the unlucky
recipient will survive.
[YURU] Mm-hmm.
[DERA] Since we're after info
on your folks,
I'd like to capture the pervert
and his daemons alive.
This guy's skilled enough
to take one of Left's arms off,
though.
I'll do my best,
but it's a tall order.
Left lost one of her arms?
The old girl honestly
took it surprisingly well.
But it just goes to show you
this guy and his katana daemons
are bad news.
No matter what happens,
I want you
to keep your distance.
-[DANJI (TSUGAI)] Oh.
-Even I'm not confident
I could dance toe-to-toe
with him,
so I'll be supporting you
from afar
with my little friend here.
I understand.
-[DANJI (TSUGAI)] Yuru.
-[YURU] Huh?
I can sense Left and Right.
This way.
[both grunt]
-[loud crash]
-[BOTH] Hm?
[YURU] Yeah, that's them.
[DERA] They're still fighting.
Sorry in advance
if we can't take the perv alive.
But risking your life
isn't an option.
If things start to go south,
I'm gonna shoot.
That said,
I'll also be ready to fire
if you give me the signal.
-Sound good?
-Hm.
[Right grunting]
[Right gasps]
[chuckles]
Was the whole spiel
about trying to take me alive
some kind of joke, or what?
That thing would've killed me!
Don't fret, lad!
I wasn't aiming
with the intent to hit you.
I can't speak for Left, though.
♪
Yuru!
[IVAN] The moon!
Damn it. He's backlit!
[grunting]
Hey, Left and Right,
I'm sorry if I hit you.
[LEFT] It matters not!
Loose your arrows!
They pose us no threat.
[Right laughs]
[YURU]
Hey, over here! Uh... pervert!
Seriously, where did this
accusation come from?
Daemon katana man! Let's talk!
I hear you have info
on my parents!
I don't like wasting arrows.
Surrender, and you can tell us
what you know.
I don't remember your parents
off the top of my head.
Maybe it would jog my memory
if you came down here.
Nice try there,
but I'm good here.
Figured. [scoffs]
Huh.
The kid's raining death
from above,
and Left and Right
have got my flanks.
What's worse,
they can keep fighting
after any injury
without a care in the world.
What a pain to deal with!
You were the one who attacked
Higashi Village, weren't you?
We've rescued the hostages,
and your buddy Shingo's
getting destroyed by
the Kagemori Clan as we speak.
What? The old man
hired all those soldiers
and still got beat?
I no longer have any reason
to negotiate with you guys.
You know about my parents.
Now, tell me everything.
Or don't, and die.
I see. I guess it's curtains
for Mr. Shingo.
Well then, it's not like
I've got any obligation
to keep serving
some washed-up nobody,
so I'll spill the beans.
Of course,
not like Shingo matters here.
He didn't have a thing
to do with your parents.
I was the one who killed
Mine and Nagisa.
[Yuru gasps]
Cut off their heads.
[Right grunts]
Now, I should prepare a gift
for my next client.
[Right growls]
[Left gasps]
Yuru needs to get Seal,
and we want it
to go nice and smooth.
Meaning, you gotta die, Left.
[Ivan grunts]
♪
[YURU] Which arm did you use
to cut down my parents?
The next shot I fire
goes into that one.
[GONZO] That so?
Well, good work, everyone.
Make sure he stays restrained
until I can get back
to the manor.
[Gonzo sighs]
They said Akio betrayed us,
just as we feared.
[Fuyuki sighs]
[Gonzo grunts]
Let's clean up this mess
so we can hurry home.
[wind blowing]
[DERA]
He decapitated Mine and Nagisa?
Really?
They'd be more useful
as hostages than corpses,
so why kill them?
Wait.
Is he lying to get a rise
out of Yuru?
Now... which arm
did I use again?
Mostly I just remember
their screams.
[Ivan chuckles]
[Yuru breathes shakily]
[MINE] Take a deep breath in
and let it out slow.
That's it. Release your breath,
and with it, all the noise
inside of your mind.
Stay calm and assess
your surroundings.
Think about what you need to do.
Consider what tools you have
on hand, in the moment.
That's how you'll survive.
I think I killed Mine
with my right arm
and Nagisa with my left.
Though, that might be backwards.
Take the bait, Yuru.
[Yuru continues
breathing shakily]
Remember, death strikes where
our fears make us vulnerable.
[Yuru grunting]
[IVAN] Waste your arrows.
What's wrong? The man
who killed your parents
is right in front of you.
Don't you wanna avenge them?
-[Yuru grunts]
-Give me an opening.
[YURU] I can't do it, Dad.
[Yuru breathing heavily]
[DERA] Keep your cool, Yuru.
Stay calm.
[Yuru grunting]
[YURU] I can't silence the noise
in my mind.
They are alive and healthy,
I'm positive.
[Yuru breathing shakily]
[exhales and inhales deeply]
[exhales deeply]
[YURU] I won't believe it
till I've seen it.
[Ivan grunts]
Put the demon katana
on the ground.
[scoffs] Boring.
Would you have me hold on
to this one?
Wow, not even that's enough
to hurt you? Good grief.
You've got a guy behind me too,
and we've established running
isn't the best option.
Pretty rough for me.
I came here to play the cat,
but somehow I wound up
as the mouse.
Well, this sucks.
I really hate
having to use this,
but you leave me no choice,
Daikyo?
[Yuru and Dera gasp]
-[squelching]
-[LEFT] Hm?
♪
Quick, Left,
lose that blasted thing!
-[Left grunts]
-[Shokyo yelps]
[Right grunts, yells]
[Right yells]
[grunts]
[Danji (Tsugai) screams]
-[LEFT] Right.
-What's wrong?
-He has done something bad.
-[RIGHT] Huh?
Get out of my way, Right!
I told you,
Lady Left's head is mine!
[RIGHT] Huh?
[Ivan grunts]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ASUMA] That wasn't
terribly nice of you.
-[DERA] Yuru!
-[ASA] Brother.
[SHINGO]
Your demons control people?
I ain't about to let 'em
hijack my body.